(Leonard:)Please don't tell anyone
(Leonard:)I spent the night
with Raj's sister.
(Sheldon:)There it is.
(Sheldon:)What if someone asks?
No one's going to ask if I spent
the night with Raj's sister.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps, but they might ask me
something else.
(Leonard:)Like what?
Like
"Has Leonard betrayed any
of his friends recently?"
(Leonard:)Priya and I are both adults.
I didn't betray Raj.
(Sheldon:)In fact, you did,
but I was referring to Howard.
(Leonard:)What are you talking about?
April 12, 2005.
(Sheldon:)Bob's Big Boy,
Toluca Lake.
(Sheldon:)Raj had just introduced us
to Priya for the first time.
(Sheldon:)She was enjoying the sweet taste
of Hindu rebellion
(Sheldon:)in the form of a Bob's
Super Big Boy hamburger.
(Sheldon:)In order
to preserve
(Sheldon:)your friendship, you and Howard
made a pinky swear
(Sheldon:)that neither of you
would attempt to woo her.
(Sheldon:)I had a patty melt.
(Leonard:)Okay, fine, I betrayed Howard.
(Sheldon:)And Raj.
All right, and Raj.
(Sheldon:)And me.
(Priya:)You?
(Sheldon:)Violation of the
Roommate Agreement's